bigcontentsearch.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy - Big Content Search

### General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) Compliance

Since 25.05.2018 all our products and services are in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), specifically on the below areas:

  * **Right to be informed:** You can ask about personal data, how it is used, and why it is being used at any time.
  * **Right of access:** You can request a copy of personal information at any time.
  * **Right of rectification:** You can update (or request updates to) personal information at any time.
  * **Right of erasure:** You may cancel your account at any time and request that we erase your personal data, cease further dissemination of the data, and potentially have third parties halt processing of the data.
  * **Right to restrict processing:** You may put your account on hold at any time.
  * **Right to object:** You can unsubscribe at anytime.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails.

The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

After you purchase our product, our email service provider will send you an email to confirm whether you want to subscribe to our newsletter, you can decide to opt-in or not.

If there is any issues with the account or payment, our system will send you a reminder email for you to check in order to proceed and continue using our service.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails from newsletter, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. You cannot unsubscribe from our system emails in case any issues with your account or payment as these emails are crucial to keep you informed about your membership status.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes, we use our own and third party cookies. For any cookies related to tracking and marketing purposes, we always ask for your consent before loading cookies to your device. 

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

We use remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

#### Google AdWords

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

Google also recommends installing the [Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) \- for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the [ Google Privacy & Terms web page](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

#### Facebook

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook [ by visiting this page](https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950)

To opt-out from Facebook's interest-based ads follow [these instructions from Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>, the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada <http://youradchoices.ca/> or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe <http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/>, or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit [Facebook's Data Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

### Governing law

This policy and the use of this site are governed by Slovenian law. This site controlled, operated and administered entirely within Slovenia. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

### Company Data

All information on the page _About_.

#### Definitions

The “site” is an online information service provided by Termitnjak Ltd. (Termitnjak Ltd.”). Wherever the agreement refers to “you” or “your”, it refers to the User of the service; “we” or “our” refers to Termitnjak Ltd.
